Come a little closer cause you looking thirsty
Imma make it better sip it like a Slurpee
Snow cone chilly
Get it free like Willy
In the jeans like Billie
You be poppin’ like a wheelie
Even in the sun you know I keep it icy
You could take a lick but it’s too cold to bite me
Brrr brrr frozen
You’re the one been chosen
Play the part like Moses
Keep it fresh like roses
Look so good yeah look so sweet
Looking good enough to eat
Coldest with this kiss so he call me ice cream
Catch me in the fridge right where the ice be
Look so good yeah look so sweet
Baby you deserve a treat
Diamonds on my wrist so he call me ice cream
You can double dip cause I know you like me
Ice cream chillin’ chillin’
Ice cream chillin’
I know that my heart could be so cold
But I’m sweet for you come put me in a cone
You’re the only touch yeah they get me melting
He’s my favorite flavor always gonna pick him
You’re the cherry piece just stay on top of me so
I can’t see nobody else for me no
Get it flip it scoop it
Do it like that ah yeah ah yeah
Like it love it lick it
Do it like lalala oh yeah
Look so good yeah look so sweet
Looking good enough to eat
Coldest with this kiss so he call me ice cream
Catch me in the fridge right where the ice be
Look so good yeah look so sweet
Baby you deserve a treat
Diamonds on my wrist so he call me ice cream
You can double dip cause I know you like me
Ice cream chillin’ chillin’
Ice cream chillin’
Ice cream
Chillin’ like a villain yeah ra ra ra
Pedal to the metal in my La Fera
So fast you keep slippin’ If you want it I just get it
Makin’ millis billis everyday
Got ice on my wrist for the summer
Keep it movin’ like my lease up
Think you fly boy where ya visa
Mona Lisa kinda Lisa
Needs an ice cream man that treats her
Keep it movin’ like my lease up
Think you fly boy where ya visa
Mona Lisa kinda Lisa
Needs an ice cream man that treats her
Na na na na na
na na na na na na na
Ice on my wrist yeah I like it like this
Get the bag with the cream
If you know what I mean
Ice cream
Ice cream chillin’
Na na na na na
na na na na na na na
Ice on my wrist yeah I like it like this
And I’m nice with the cream
If you know what I mean
Ice cream